翻译: 扭头 149  王一流先生
不 不不不
No! No, no, no!
你不能把她从我身边带走 混蛋
You can't take her from me, you bastard!
校对: 王一流先生
别这样 Scully
Don't do this, Scully.
你现在必须为了她而坚强
You have to be strong for her right now.
怎么回事
What's going on?
后期: C 君
贩卖机要换了
Unit's being replaced.
- 别啊  - 不行
- Come on! - No!
这台机器在这儿呆了一辈子了
That machine's been here forever.
已经成为警队的一员了
It's basically part of the force.
压制: 凯撒
还是把Scully带走吧
Take Scully instead.
是的 拜托了 带我去自动贩卖机乐园吧
Yes, please, take me to the land of vending machines.
可以至少给我们五分钟好好道别吗
Can we at least have five minutes to say a proper good-bye?
随便你们
Whatever.
就让我简要地开个场
Let me just start by saying
这台机器是布鲁克林最棒的餐馆
that this machine is the best restaurant in Brooklyn,
而且永远都有我的位子
and it always had a table for me.
我是那么清楚 打它哪里才能掉出来免费食物
I knew just where to punch it to get free food.
现在我又要回去打Hitchcock了
Now I have to go back to punching Hitchcock.
看啊 我要求他们放进去的那袋小胡萝卜
Look, she still has the bags of baby carrots
依然还在里面
I requested they put in.
它们现在变黑了 但是至少还在那儿
They're black now, but they're there.
再见了 美丽的机器
Good-bye, beautiful machine.
感谢你的服务
Thank you for your service.
好了 全体敬礼
Okay, squad salute.
你现在可以带她走了
You can take her away now.
我觉得我们让它有尊严地离去了
Well, I think we handled that with dignity.
免费拿糖啦
Free candy!
神烦警探
第二季 第二十三集
电波诚译
好了 九九片区 跟Michael Augustine问好吧
Okay. Nine-Nine, say hello to Michael Augustine,
布鲁克林最高产的身份盗窃犯
Brooklyn's most prolific identity thief.
上周他走进一栋政府大楼
Last week, he walked into a government building
偷走了一台存有十万多个社保号码的电脑
and stole a computer containing over 100,000 social security numbers.
我的线人说今晚Augustine
My C.I. Says that tonight Augustine
会把电脑交给一个从中国来的买家
will be handing off the laptop to a buyer from China,
中国又名"龙之大陆"
AKA the Land of Dragons.
确保你不会把这个词用在正式报告里
Make sure that phrase is not in your official report.
好吧 对不起
Okay, sorry,
"龙之国度"
The Country of Dragons.
我希望你和Santiago跟踪Augustine
I want you and Santiago to tail Augustine
直到他交货然后逮捕他和买家
until he makes the drop, and then arrest him and the buyer.
听起来不错 不过我带Boyle去就好了
Sounds good, although I could probably just take Boyle.
我知道Amy有一堆工作要做 所以
I know Amy has a ton of work, so...
- 我没有啊  - 真的吗
- No, I don't. - Really?
我保证我不小心听到你跟Rosa说
I could have sworn I overheard you telling Rosa,
"姐们儿 拜托"
"Girlfriend, please.
"我有一筐砸的案件要破"
I got hella open cases."
你认为我会这么说话吗
That's something you think I said?
一字不差
Word for word.
一点儿没胡诌
No diggity, no doubt.
够了
That's enough.
Peralta和Santiago跟踪Augustine
Peralta and Santiago will tail Augustine.
Boyle和Diaz跟他们一起开监视车去
Boyle and Diaz will join them in a surveillance van
除非你还有异议
unless you have a problem with that.
听起来好极了
Sounds great.
就像Amy Santiago一直说的
In the immortal words of Amy Santiago,
"姐们儿 拜托"
"Girlfriend, please."
我是做了什么对不起你的事吗
Hey, did I do something to you?
你在生我气吗
Are you mad?
是因为我把你桌上的面包屑都扫掉了吗
Is this because I brushed all the crumbs off your desk?
什么 不 我才不在乎那个
What? No, I don't care about that.
- 你知道它们在哪儿吗  - 垃圾桶里
- Do you know where they are? - In the trash.
好吧 如果不是那个
All right, if it's not that,
你为什么不想让我参与这个案子
then why are you trying to keep me off this case?
哦 那个啊
Oh, that.
好吧 听着
All right, look,
我不想跟你合作的原因是
the reason that I didn't want to work with you is...
我可以用口音来说
should I do this in an accent
好让自己不感觉那么尴尬吗
so that I can undercut some of the awkwardness I'm feeling?
- 不行  - 明智
- No. - Good call.
记得你说过你不想和警察约会吗
Remember when you told me that you didn't want to date cops?
真真儿地打击到我了啊 大兄弟
That really bummed me out, man.
- 牙买加吗  - 是啊 错误的选择
- Jamaican? - Yeah, it was a bad choice.
我的德国口音好多了
I'm much better at German.
好了 好吧
All right, fine.
我本来有点想约你出去的
I was kind of thinking about asking you out.
噢 好吧
Oh, okay.
但我知道你不想
But I know that that's not what you want,
我完全明白
and I totally get it.
我觉得我只是需要一点时间来完全地完全明白
I think it just took me a while to totally-totally get it,
而现在我完全明白了
and now I totally get it.
Jake 这太尴尬了
Jake, this is weird.
我不和警察约会的根本原因
The whole point of me not dating cops
就是为了让工作时候不尴尬
is so it wouldn't be weird at work.
好吧 那让这不尴尬就好了 是吧
Okay, so let's just make it not weird, right?
这只是个案子 我们一直一起破案的
This is a case; we work cases together all the time,
而且我们真的很擅长破案
and we're really good at it,
所以 你知道的 我们很专业
so, you know, we're professionals.
那就是我想要的 让我们保持专业
That's all I want, for us to be professional.
我们达成共识了
We're in agreement.
保证是贼好贼专业
It will be good and professional.
进来关上门
Come in and shut the door.
我有些消息要宣布而你们必须保证保密
I have some news, which you must promise to keep secret.
Madeline Wuntch要把我调去当纽约警察的公关部长
Madeline Wuntch is making me head of public relations for the NYPD.
我要被踢出九九片区了
I'm being forced out of the Nine-Nine.
我不想小题大做
I don't wish to make a big deal of it,
所以请你们把反应缩短到一秒 开始
so please limit your reactions to one second; go.
- 什么情况  - 你在开玩笑吗
- What in the world? - Are you kidding me?
够了
That's plenty.
你不能离开我们
You can't leave us.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
Madeline不是什么无敌女妖
Madeline's not some invincible succubus.
她只是个普通女妖 而且是可以战胜的
She's a regular succubus, and she can be defeated.
我们只需要找到"那封信"
We just need to find the letter.
什么信
What letter?
在我们现任公安局长上任之前
Before our current police commissioner was hired,
一位共同的好友告诉我Madeline写了封信给市长
a mutual friend told me Madeline wrote a letter to the mayor
告诉他这是个错误
telling him it was a mistake.
她显然有把自己的上司叫做
She apparently called her now-boss
一个 上引号 假笑的蠢蛋 下引号
a "Simpering buffoon".
不专业 损人就得当面损
Amateur; always say your insults to someone's face.
不留书面证据
No paper trail.
那封信的副本被存在市长的档案室里
A copy of that letter exists in the mayor's archives.
我不可能在不引起Madeline注意的情况下潜入
I can't go snooping around without alerting Madeline,
所以这不是易事 我们也没多少时间了
so it won't be easy, and we don't have much time,
但我需要你们去找到那封信
but I need you to find that letter.
你们愿意帮我吗
Are you with me?
当然
Oh, hell yeah.
我把我手机调成飞行模式了
I'm turning my phone into airplane mode.
哦天呐 她在飞机上都不那么做的
Oh, my God, she doesn't even do that on airplanes.
Rosa
Rosa,
我知道你不希望任何人祝你生日快乐
I know you don't like anyone wishing you a happy birthday,
所以享受糟糕的一天吧
so crappy day to you.
还是太过了
Still too much.
我猜你今晚是没什么庆祝的安排咯
I assume you're not doing anything to celebrate tonight.
任何超过六岁还在庆生的人 都该下地狱
Anyone over the age of six celebrating a birthday should go to hell.
既然你有空
So since you're free,
我需要你帮我搬一台我刚买的旧吃豆人机
I need your help moving this old Ms. Pac-Man machine I just bought.
为什么你怎么喜欢这游戏
Why are you so obsessed with that game?
因为这是史上最性感的电子游戏
Because it's the sexiest video game ever.
她是欲求不满的 Rosa
She's insatiable, Rosa.
欲求不满的 欲求不
Insatiable. Insatiab...
别再说"欲求不满"了
Stop saying "Insatiable."
总之 这旧机器我是从一家酒吧买来的
Anyway, I bought this old machine from a bar,
所以我希望你能帮我搬它
and I was hoping you'd help me move it.
你想让我去酒吧
You want me to go to a bar?
你明显是想引诱我参加惊喜派对
You are obviously trying to get me to go to a surprise party.
是Marcus让你来的吗
Did Marcus put you up to this?
什么 不 瞎说什么呢
What? No, that's crazy talking.
我们只是需要正好晚上九点四十五到那儿
We just need to be there at exactly 9:45 p.m.
一分都不能早
and not a minute earlier.
而且我想让咱们走过一扇特定的门
Also, there's a particular door I want us to enter through.
他怎么在这儿下车了
Why is he getting out here?
我以为你的线人是说他会在公园交货
I thought your C.I. Said the drop was happening in a park.
或许他要先和小三吃个晚饭
Maybe he's having dinner with his sidepiece first.
Augustine把电脑带着了
Augustine has the laptop with him.
我们应该就在这儿逮捕他
We should just arrest him right here.
不 买家是更重要的人
No, the buyer's the bigger collar.
我们必须跟着他 直到他们碰头
We've got to follow him in and wait for the handoff.
好吧 如果你们要进去
Okay, if you're going in,
我听说这地方的骨髓蛋糊超棒
I've heard this place has an amazing bone marrow custard.
也不是说我吃过不好的
Not that I've ever had a bad one.
不 就这样了 进去吧
No. All right, let's go.
不 等等 我们看起来太像警察了
No, wait, we look like cops.
这样我们根本混不进去
We're never gonna blend in dressed like this.
好了 现在怎么样
Okay, there, how's that?
呃 我不知道啊
Uh, I don't know.
我看到的只是衣服挂在无性别的肉身上
All I see is clothes hanging off of a genderless blob.
你看起来很好 给 穿上这个
You look fine. Here, wear this.
Jake 你得穿件外套什么的
Jake, you need a jacket or something.
Scully把他的运动大衣留在后面了
Well, Scully left his sports coat back there.
哦 但它肯定配不上Jake健美的身躯
Oh, but it will never fit Jake's athletic body.
- 除非  - 不 我不想那么做
- Unless... - No, I don't want to do that.
- 你不得不  - 我不会做的
- You have to. - I'm not gonna do it.
你要做的
You're doing it.
什么 你必须做什么
What? What do you have to do?
唐·约翰逊范儿
Don Johnson it.
唐·约翰逊 美国制片人 总是卷袖口
唐·约翰逊范儿
Don Johnson it!
我看起来跟个傻子似的
I look like an idiot.
我都没来得及给小臂上个润肤露
I didn't even have time to lotion my forearms.
穿着Rosa的外套感觉太奇怪了
It's so weird wearing Rosa's jacket.
口袋里有根带刺铁丝
There's a piece of barbed wire in the pocket.
酷
Cool.
好了 你有看到
All right, do you have a visual on...
服务台吗
the hostess stand?
嗨 两个人 谢谢
Hi. Table for two, please.
很抱歉 没有空位了
I'm so sorry. There's nothing available.
我们餐厅已经被订满了
We're totally booked up.
哦不 太糟糕了
Oh, no, that's horrible.
今晚对我们来说可重要了
Tonight's a really important night for us.
Johnny和我刚订婚
Johnny and I just got engaged,
而这是我们第一次约会的地方
and this is where our first date was.
哦是啊 这对Dora和我太重要了
Oh, yeah, it would mean so much to Dora and me.
我是应该提前预订的
I would have made a reservation,
但是我不确定她会不会答应我的求婚 所以
but I didn't know if she was gonna say yes, so...
我就喜欢你紧张的样子 你这小呆鹅
Oh, I love how nervous you were, you little goose.
你俩太甜蜜了
You are just so sweet together.
我肯定能给你们小两口找到位置
You know, I'm sure I can find room for two young lovers.
是啊 我们是小两口 一起 在床上
Yeah, we are lovers... together... in beds.
好吧
Okay.
感谢你们耐心等了这么久
Thank you so much for waiting.
你们的桌子马上就收拾好了
Your table is almost ready.
好
Great.
不好意思 突然对你使出订婚和这些暧昧的招
Sorry about springing the engagement and romantic stuff on you.
不不不 挺好
No, no, no. That was great.
我是说 好歹让咱成功进来了
I mean, it's what got us in here.
亲脸颊有点过了 湿嗒嗒的
Cheek kiss was a bit much. Very wet.
怎么说呢
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
Dora吻技一般
Dora's sloppy.
好了 请跟我来
Okay, and if you'll just follow me.
蜜月期结束了 Dora
Well, the honeymoon's over, Dora.
回归Jake和Amy
We're back to being Jake and Amy,
两个一起办案的普通警察
two normal cops working a job.
到了 请坐
All right, there you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
你们是那对刚订婚的情侣
You're the couple that just got engaged.
的确是我们 Johnny和Dora 绝对的情侣
That's us, Johnny and Dora, a couple for sure.
好的 根据我从助理界得来的消息
Okay, according to my sources in the assistant community,
那封信就在这里 四楼档案室
the letter is right here in the fourth-floor archives,
J-13柜
cabinet J-13.
好样的 什么计划
Nice job. What's the plan?
你溜进去拿到信
You sneak in and get the letter.
我来转移档案员的注意力
I'll distract the file clerk.
据说他很喜欢观察鸟类
Apparently, he's very into bird watching,
所以跟女人说话应该会让他晕过去
so talking to a woman should blow his mind.
而跟这位女人说话
And talking to this woman,
没准能让他猝死过去
it could kill him.
你能帮我看看这公园的地图
Here, can you look at this map of a park
告诉我哪里能看到那些漂亮的鸟呢
and tell me where them hot birds hang out?
嗯 你要 呃 别去 呃
Well, you're gonna want to, uh, avoid the, uh,
大草坪 因为那里基本都是八哥
great lawn, because it's basically just grackles.
- 恶 八哥  - 是啊
- Ugh, grackles? - Yeah.
我讨厌八哥
I hate grackles.
最差的品种了
They're the worst.
在这有好多人觉得八哥是一种常见的鸟
Well, a lot of people think grackles are just a common bird up here,
但是你知道吗
but you know what?
在西海岸没有八哥
On the West Coast they don't get grackles.
你能再分享些经验
Can you give some more info
给我这样一个新手鸟类观察者吗
for a novice bird watcher such as myself?
你一定得知道
You have got to know the difference
各种水鸟间的差别
between your water birds.
好多人根本不知道
I mean, so many people don't know the difference
蛇鹈 蛇鸟 水火鸡的区别
between an anhinga and a snake bird and a swamp hawk.
好多人都不知道它们其实是一种鸟类
A lot of people don't know they're all the same bird.
是哪种叫起来声音像蕾哈娜的鸟吗
Are those the ones that sound like Rihanna kind of when they sing?
我不太清楚那是谁
I'm not familiar with who that is.
就像这样 "诶 诶"
They're like, "Eh, eh."
听起来像有冠啄木鸟
That sounds like that might be a crested woodpecker.
或者这种
Or is it more like...
那有可能是有冠山雀
Well, that's a crested titmouse maybe?
哎呦天啊 就是这个
Oh, my God, that's it.
Wayne 你简直是个宝贝
Wayne, you are a damn treasure trove.
我们拿到信了
We got the letter.
好样的
Well done.
现在把Madeline叫来 再拿一桶水
Now get me Madeline and a bucket of water.
<绿野仙踪>中邪恶的西方女巫被女主角泼了一桶水后融化而死
让我们好好化了这巫婆
It's time to melt a witch.
还有谁在
Who else is going?
Rosa 听我说 没有什么派对
Rosa, listen to me, there is no party.
别纠缠这事不放了
Just get off my doughnut already.
别骗我 Boyle
Don't lie to me, Boyle,
否则你就等着拿个吸管吃自己的骨髓蛋糊吧
or you will be eating your bone marrow custard through a straw.
其实骨髓蛋糊并不是这么吃的
That's exactly how you're supposed to eat bone marrow...
Charles
Charles!
好吧是有个派对
All right, there's a party.
我不能告诉你细节
I can't give you details.
我只能说我了解你
All I can say is I know you,
所以我知道你会喜欢的
and I know you'll have a good time.
如果你了解我 你就会知道我讨厌这种惊喜派对
If you knew me, you'd know I hate surprise parties,
所以很显然你并不了解我
so clearly you don't know me at all.
什么 我们可是朋友啊
What? We're friends.
我还指望能咱们能亲近到可以叫你"Roro"呢
I was building up to calling you "Ro-ro" One of these days.
永远不能
That will never happen.
其实 你刚才已经失去叫我"Rosa"的特权了
In fact, you just lost "Rosa" Privileges.
从现在开始 你只能叫我"Diaz"或者"说你呢"
From now on, you can call me "Diaz" Or "Hey, you."
别这样 Rosa
Come on, Rosa.
别这样 "说你呢"
Come on, hey, you.
哇 香槟和牡蛎
Wow, champagne and oysters.
你们真是太热情了
You really shouldn't have, guys.
哎 这是个特别的晚上嘛
Well, it's a special night.
你们什么时候见面的
So when did you guys meet?
- 去年  - 五年前
- Last year. - Five years ago.
我们最开始在五年前见过一面
We first met five years ago,
但是那次就不算了 因为
but we don't count it, because...
我当时在跟一个快艇模特交往
I was dating a speedboat model at the time.
我当时在和美国大城市来的一个超帅的审计长交往
And I was dating a super handsome comptroller of a major U.S. City.
总之一年前我们在一个酒吧里重逢了
Anyways, about a year ago, we bumped into each other at a bar,
从那以后我们就难舍难分了
and we haven't been able to keep our hands off each other since.
你是怎么认准她就是你那命中注定的另一半呢
So how did you know she was the one?
我太愿意回答这个问题了
I'd love to answer that.
就是吧 每当我看到她的脸
Um, you know, just whenever I look at her face
还有那下面连着的身子
and the attached physique.
你呢
And you?
他总能逗我笑
He makes me laugh.
还有
And, you know,
这世上我最在乎的就是她的想法了 所以
there's really no one else's opinion who I care about more than hers, so...
好把 别的先不聊 让我们看看那戒指
Okay, so enough chitchat Let's see the ring.
我这次没戴着
I don't have it on me.
她有巨大的手指
She has gigantic fingers.
我刚才的意思是
What I mean to say is that
我买的那戒指跟她手指不合适
the ring I got would never have fit on her fingers,
因为那些手指的主人是个庞然大物
because they are that of a giant, behemoth person.
Madeline 谢谢你能来
Madeline, thank you for coming.
Raymond 我永远乐意拜访一个被我打败的敌人
Raymond, always a pleasure to call on a vanquished foe.
我觉得自己就像Jackie Joyner-Kersee
I feel like Jackie Joyner-Kersee
Jackie Joyner-Kersee 多次获得跳远及七项全能奥运金牌的女运动员
祝贺某个跑得慢的失败者
congratulating one of the other slower runners.
准备好
Buckle up.
暴风雨要来了
It's gonna be a hell of a ride.
坐吗
Care to sit?
我相信你一定想歇歇自己的分趾蹄子
I'm sure you'd like to take some weight off your cloven hooves.
叫我魔鬼吗
Calling me the devil?
分趾蹄常被人们与西方传说中的恶魔联系在一起
真有创意啊 Raymond
How original, Raymond.
事实上我在叫你山羊 你个山羊
Actually I was calling you a goat, you goat.
我想谈谈我升职的问题
I'd like to talk about my promotion.
好的 但是首先
Very well, but first,
我怎么知道你是不是带了窃听器
how do I know you're not wearing a wire?
我需要先搜你身
I need to pat you down.
如果你非要的话
If you must.
这什么情况啊
What is going on?
嘘 我看东西呢
Shh. I'm watching something.
你能帮我从泊车员那里把车取来吗 亲爱的
Can you get the car from the valet, babe?
我要去后面跟主厨打个招呼
I'm gonna in the back and say hi to the chef.
祝你们婚礼一切顺利
Good luck on your wedding, guys.
还有蜜月快乐哦
Oh, have fun on your honeymoon.
我们会的 我们要去德州韦科市
We will. We're going to Waco, Texas.
好吧 拜拜
Okay, bye.
拜
Bye.
- 德州韦科市  - 我瞎说的
- Waco, Texas? - I don't know.
正好在新闻上看见了而已
It was just on Dateline.
好吧 Augustine拿着笔记本包呢
All right, well, Augustine took the laptop case with him.
他要准备交接了 走
He's gonna make the drop. Let's go.
看 那就是买家了
Look, there's the buyer.
或者他真是去跟主厨打招呼的
Or maybe he's just actually saying hi to the chef?
他怎么还没交接
Why isn't he making the handoff?
不好 他看见我们了
Oh, crap, he saw us.
不好意思
Excuse me.
哦 嘿
Oh, hey.
我们就是想找个地方
We were just looking for a place to, uh...
打炮
Boink.
是 打炮
Yep. Boink.
也是我的首选词汇
That's my preferred term for it as well.
我懂得
I get it.
刚刚订婚的孩子们 玩得开心
Newly engaged kids. Enjoy.
谢了
Thanks.
好好好好好
Good. Good, good, good, good.
没暴露 好样的
We kept our cover intact. Nice work.
快速并专业的反应
Quick, professional thinking out there.
非常快非常专业
Very quick Very professional.
- 不愧是警探  - 真乃警探
- Detective. - Detective.
- 继续回到案子上  - 是
- Let's get back on the case. - Yes.
餐厅怎么样啊
So how was the restaurant?
正常得不得了
Such a normal time!
你怎么那么奇怪
Why are you being weird?
我和Amy接吻了
Amy and I kissed.
啥
What?
只是为了不暴露卧底身份 我们没有别的选择
To keep our cover from being blown; we didn't have a choice.
快告诉我所有细节
Tell me everything!
Charles 只是个吻而已 好吗
Charles, it was just a kiss, okay?
为了工作的 根本没什么
It was for work. It was nothing.
就是 一个吻谁在乎
Yeah, who cares about a kiss?
真到互相摸屁股的地步再叫我
Call me if you grab each other's asses.
他靠边停了 就是现在了
He's pulling over. It's going down.
你们太天真了
You guys are so naive.
这不可能只是"没什么"
It's never nothing.
高中的时候 我扮演<安妮>里面的沃巴克斯爸爸
In high school, I played Daddy Warbucks in Annie,
<安妮> 百老汇音乐剧 剧中沃巴克斯爸爸收养了女主角安妮
Becca Murse扮演安妮
Becca Murse played Annie,
我们在台上有一段拥抱的戏
and we were supposed to hug onstage.
刚开始我们也没觉得有什么大不了
And at first, that seemed like nothing too,
但是首演夜上 我们就开始大搞特搞了
but by opening night, we were full-on making out.
扮成沃巴克斯和安妮的时候吗
As Daddy Warbucks and Annie?
是的哟
Mm-hmm.
观众们纷纷表示不买账
The audience was not on board.
剧作家还把学校给告了
Playwright sued the school.
伙计们 他们没打算碰头
Guys, guys, it's not a handoff.
他正在放下包裹
He's leaving the package.
好的 你和Rosa跟住Augustine
Okay, you and Rosa follow Augustine.
好嘞
Right!
你和Amy也跟住了自己的心吧
And you and Amy follow your hearts.
什么玩意儿 我们要守着包裹
No, we're gonna stay with the package.
也要和对方长相厮守
And each other forever.
你闹毛线啊
Come on, man!
那么 我看这件事的到后来会是这样的
So here's how I see this going down.
你哀求我把工作还给你 我拒绝了
You plead for your job back. I refuse.
然后你就像个战后遗孀一样嘤嘤地抹眼泪
You start weeping like a war widow.
你说是不是这样啊
Does that sound about right?
你那一肚子坏水恐怕是派不上用场了 Madeline
Don't count your gross fish babies before they've hatched, Madeline.
你是怎么搞到这个的
How did you get this?
这是Gina和Terry搞到的 你个八哥
Gina and Terry got it, you grackle.
这东西是怎么搞来的并不重要
It doesn't matter how I got it.
抱歉长官 我没意识到你要这么说
Sorry, sir, didn't realize that was how you wanted to play it.
你还请了观众来看自己耍把戏吗
I see you've got an audience for this little stunt?
是啊 谁不想看勇者斗鳄鱼呢
Yes, well, who wouldn't want to see a man fight a crocodile?
那么 Madeline
Now, Madeline
在我俩中有人"像个战后遗孀一样嘤嘤地抹眼泪"之前
before one of us starts "weeping like a war widow,"
你愿不愿意把我的片区还给我呢
would you like to give me my precinct back?
这事不是那么简单的 我不能撤销你的升职
It's not that simple; I can't just reverse your promotion.
那你明天之前作出决定吧
You have until tomorrow,
你个八哥
you grackle.
我们不能在放货点旁边抓他
We can't pull him over this close to the drop site.
会惊动买家
It'll alert the buyer.
我们先跟他一英里再说吧
I say we follow him for a mile.
明白
Copy that.
你在你妈妈三月二十六日的生日上送她的手机
How's your mom enjoying the new phone you got her
她用着顺不顺手啊
for her birthday on March 16th?
哥们 别靠胡诌以前的事情来跟我套近乎
Dude, stop saying random facts to try to prove you know me.
我才没有套近乎呐
That's not what I'm doing.
我只是在和好朋友Rosa聊聊天
I'm simply making small talk with my friend Rosa,
话说她玩过高空跳伞
who went skydiving once.
够了
Enough!
我会去那个白痴派对的
I'm going to the dumb party
但只是因为我不想伤Marcus的心而已
but only because I don't want to hurt Marcus.
别以为我已经不生你的气了
I'm still super mad at you.
你是不是也还因为<吉尔莫女孩>的大结局生气啊
Mm, like how you're still super mad at Gilmore Girls for how the finale went down?
<吉尔莫女孩> 华纳兄弟推出的一部有关家庭、友情和爱情的系列电视剧
我就是想看到Lorelai得到幸福
I just want to see Lorelai happy,
Lorelai 剧中的叛逆女性
你给我闭嘴
and shut up!
你看吧
Ah, see?
我和你都这么熟了 我就知道会这
I knew you so well, I knew it was co...
说真的 我们啥事都没有吧
Hey, seriously, we're cool, right?
那当然
Yeah, totally.
- 我们很好  - 好
- We're fine. - Good.
天哪 肚子都有点饿了
Gosh, you know, I'm actually a little bit hungry.
在那个蛋疼的高级餐厅里 我一口饭都没吃
I never ended up eating at that dumb fancy restaurant.
你猜我回家的时候会吃点什么
You know what I'm getting on my way home?
你肯定是去路上的波兰餐厅
Yeah, you're gonna go to the Polish place
吃波兰饺子 土豆煎饼 还有一杯热巧克力
and get perogies, potato pancakes, and a cup of hot chocolate.
你说的一点儿没错
That's exactly what I'm gonna get.
那可不
Yeah.
我打算吃披萨
I will be having pizza,
来两块托尼披萨店的至尊红肉披萨
two slices of meat supreme from Tony's,
就要刚从展台上拿下来的温度
served display temperature.
至尊红肉披萨已经够可怕的了
Meat supreme is a million red flags,
你凉着吃是想逆天吗
and eating it cold is just insane.
不不不 并不是凉着吃
No, no, no. It's not cold.
- 而是刚从展台上拿下来的温度  - Jake
- It's display temperature. - Jake.
Amy 这中间还是有区别的
There's a difference, Amy.
不是 Jake 他在盯着我们看
No, Jake, he's looking at us.
那就这只好这样了
Well, this is happening.
纽约警局 不许动
NYPD! Freeze!
我们是警局同事
We are police colleagues!
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
这可是工作场合
This is a work event.
你签一下对Augustine和买家的逮捕报告吧
Hey, can you sign this arrest report for Augustine and the buyer?
没问题
Sure.
好的
Great.
我都忘了你签字要花上多长时间了
Man, I forgot how long your signature takes.
请容我马上用手机看完<勇敢的心>
I'm just gonna watch Braveheart on my phone real quick.
<勇敢的心> 梅尔·吉布森执导的战争片
鉴于现状
Given the circumstances,
我知道刚才的事情看起来很像是调情
I could see how that might have seemed like flirty teasing or something,
但我当时真的很不满
but I was legit being critical.
你要摊上大事了
You have a problem.
不对 这话现在听着都像在开玩笑
No, even that sounded like banter now.
好吧 我只有一条出路了
All right, there's only one way out of this for me.
我会变得超级残忍
I just got to get super cruel.
准备好被我指出生理缺陷吧 Amy
Prepare to have your physical flaws pointed out, Amy.
瞧你那高高的屁股和诡异的胳膊肘
I'm talking about your tall butt and your weird elbows.
Jake 没关系的
Jake, it's okay.
多谢
Thank you.
今晚真是太奇怪了
This whole night was really weird.
没错啊
I know.
我只是
I just...
真希望我们可以回到从前
I want everything to go back how it was, you know?
这是在太尴尬了
It's so awkward.
- 没错  - 你说得对
- Yeah. - And you're right.
我们不应该和警察谈对象
We shouldn't date cops,
因为我们是个很厉害的团队
'cause we're a great team.
我们在一起工作得很好
We work great together.
我不想把这种关系搞砸
I don't want to mess that up.
是啊 我也不想这些事都变味儿
Yeah, I don't want everything to change.
我也不想
Yeah, me neither.
好啊 那么一言为定了
Okay, then that's that,
Peralta探员
Detective Peralta.
Santiago探员
Detective Santiago.
片区里再见了
See you around the precinct.
是的
Yep.
高高的屁股
Tall butt.
好 在我们进去之前
Okay, before we go in,
记得一定要装出惊喜的样子
remember you have to pretend to be surprised.
这个怎么样
How's this?
天惹噜
Oh, my God.
这比我想象中的还要蛋疼哟
It's so much worse than I imagined.
你这精神面貌很好 但是传达的信息不太对
The energy was great, but the message was flawed.
得了吧 赶紧进去就完事了
All right, let's get this over with.
惊喜哟
Surprise.
什么情况
What's going on?
我租下了整个酒吧
I rented this entire bar
这样我们就可以边庆祝边享受二人世界了
so you and I could celebrate with no people anywhere near us.
话说我倒是该雇个酒保的
I probably should have hired a bartender, though.
我根本不会调酒
I have no idea how to make drinks.
太不可思议了
This is incredible.
这些都是Charles的点子
It was all Charles' idea.
都说了我懂你的 Roro
I told you I knew you, Ro-ro.
谢谢你
Thank you.
再敢叫老娘一句"Roro"试试
But never call me "Ro-ro" Again.
试试就试试
Oh, but I will.
这是我应得的报偿
I've earned this.
生日快乐呀 Roro
Happy b-day, Ro-ro.
欢迎光临 Madeline 你打好主意了吗
Welcome, Madeline. Have you thought things over?
打好了
I have,
但首先 我怎么知道你是不是带了窃听器
but first, how do I know you're not wearing a wire?
8分钟后
于是 我把事情想了一遍
So I've thought it over,
还是让你把那封信交给局长好了
and perhaps you should go ahead and show that letter to the commissioner.
让他炒了你吗
And let him fire you?
我会否认信是我写的
I'll deny I wrote it.
认证调查将花上几个月的时间
It will take months to authenticate,
那么我就会有足够的时间
which will give me plenty of time
来给这里做一些人事调整
to make some personnel changes around here.
布莱顿海滩那边正好缺一个警探
There's an opening for a detective down in Brighton Beach.
我就把Diaz调过去好了
I think I'll transfer Diaz there.
然后把Boyle探员调到长岛市
Detective Boyle I'll send to Long Island City.
Santiago一定很适合佩兰港
Santiago will be a great fit for Pelham Bay.
还有你的心头肉 Peralta
And Peralta, your little pet project,
我会把他输送到史泰登岛去
I'm gonna ship him off to Staten Island.
但愿他喜欢去英勇阻止日光浴沙龙间的斗拳
Hope he likes breaking up tanning salon fistfights.
看来轮到你做出决断了呢 Raymond
Looks like you've got a decision to make, Raymond.
你打算怎样
What are you gonna do?
队员们 请听我说几句
Squad, if I could have your attention please?
我要被调到公关部了
I am being transferred to the public relations office.
我会当即离开九九片区
I'm leaving the Nine-Nine effective immediately.
什么鬼啊
What the hell?
我没懂你说什么
I don't understand.
什么鬼啊
What the hell?
你为什么要这样
Why are you doing this?
什么鬼啊啊啊
What the hell?
我想说
I want to say
非常荣幸能在过去的二十一又二分之一个月里和诸位共事
it has been a pleasure to have worked alongside all of you for the past 21 1/2 months.
希望大家能谅解我这无法控制的情绪
I'm sorry for getting so emotional.
其实你这语气和以前是一样的
A pretty consistent tone, actually.
这几年是
These have been the...
这几年是我的职业生涯中最美好的时光
these have been the best years of my career.
不好了 这我可没见过
Oh, no. This is new.
我知道你们每个人都为我倾尽所有
And I know that everyone of you gave me everything you had,
对此我将毕生感激
and I will never forget it.
快点变回机器人警监啊
Go back to being robot captain.
嘎 吱
Meep-morp.
叽
Zeet.
解散
Dismissed.
长官
Sir!
我要和你一起走
I'm coming with you.
谢谢你 Gina
Thank you, Gina.
我也和你一起
I'm also coming.
不必了
Not necessary.
你好
Hey.
就知道会在这找到你
Thought I might find you in here.
我得消化一下警监离开的事
I just needed to process the captain's news.
我真的太为他感到难过了
I feel so bad for him.
那你现在感觉怎么样了
So how are you holding up?
不知道 我还没缓过劲来
I don't know. I'm still in shock.
你呢
You?
和我爸弃我而去的时候差不多
Um, basically handling it the way I dealt with my dad leaving,
我就把这些感情都憋到烂在肚子里为止
just repressing the hell out of it.
所以这里最近真是风云莫测呢
So a lot of change around here, huh?
Jake快来 新的警监到了
Hey, Jake, the new captain's here.
你觉得会是谁
Who do you think it's gonna be?
没想过
I have no idea.
说不定是我呢
I bet it's me.
但愿我已经准备好了
I just hope I'm ready.
哇哦
Wow.
打起精神来 各位
Come on, guys.
我知道你们很难过
I know you're sad,
可我们得尽力给人家留个好的第一印象
but let's do our best to make a good first impression here.
机智 说的没错
Smart. Good call.
Jake 你站前面去
Jake, you be up front.
喔
Oh!
好了 让我们瞧瞧
Okay, here we go.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组